Guide to the Walter Tobriner papers, 1949-1968 MS2014
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
- Scrapbooks, 1961-1968; MS2014 Series 5; 8 Linear feet
  - Page 186, 1966-1967 (Box 17, Folder 79)
  - Page 187, 1966-1967 (Box 17, Folder 80)
  - Page 188, 1966-1967 (Box 17, Folder 81)
  - Page 189, 1966-1967 (Box 17, Folder 82)
  - Page 190, 1966-1967 (Box 17, Folder 83)
  - Page 191, 1966-1967 (Box 17, Folder 84)
  - Page 192, 1966-1967 (Box 17, Folder 85)
  - Page 193, 1966-1967 (Box 17, Folder 86)
  - Page 194, 1966-1967 (Box 17, Folder 87)
  - Page 195, 1966-1967 (Box 17, Folder 88)
  - Page 196, 1966-1967 (Box 17, Folder 89)
  - Page 197, 1966-1967 (Box 17, Folder 90)
  - Page 198, 1966-1967 (Box 17, Folder 91)
  - Page 199, 1966-1967 (Box 17, Folder 92)
  - Page 200, 1966-1967 (Box 17, Folder 93)
  - Page 201, 1966-1967 (Box 17, Folder 94)
  - Page 202, 1966-1967 (Box 17, Folder 95)
  - Page 203, 1966-1967 (Box 17, Folder 96)
  - Page 204, 1966-1967 (Box 17, Folder 97)
  - Page 205, 1966-1967 (Box 17, Folder 98)
  - Page 206, 1966-1967 (Box 17, Folder 99)
  - Page 207, 1966-1967 (Box 17, Folder 100)
  - Page 208, 1966-1967 (Box 17, Folder 101)
  - Page 209, 1966-1967 (Box 17, Folder 102)
  - Page 210, 1966-1967 (Box 18, Folder 1)
  - Page 211, 1966-1967 (Box 18, Folder 2)
  - Page 212, 1966-1967 (Box 18, Folder 3)
  - Page 213, 1966-1967 (Box 18, Folder 4)
  - Page 214, 1966-1967 (Box 18, Folder 5)
  - Page 215, 1966-1967 (Box 18, Folder 6)
  - Page 216, 1966-1967 (Box 18, Folder 7)
  - Page 217, 1966-1967 (Box 18, Folder 8)
  - Page 218, 1966-1967 (Box 18, Folder 9)
  - Page 219, 1966-1967 (Box 18, Folder 10)
  - Page 220, 1966-1967 (Box 18, Folder 11)
  - Page 221, 1966-1967 (Box 18, Folder 12)
  - Page 222, 1966-1967 (Box 18, Folder 13)
  - Page 223, 1966-1967 (Box 18, Folder 14)
  - Page 224, 1966-1967 (Box 18, Folder 15)
  - Page 225, 1966-1967 (Box 18, Folder 16)
  - Page 226, 1966-1967 (Box 18, Folder 17)
  - Page 227, 1966-1967 (Box 18, Folder 18)
  - Page 228, 1966-1967 (Box 18, Folder 19)
  - Page 229, 1966-1967 (Box 18, Folder 20)
  - Page 230, 1966-1967 (Box 18, Folder 21)
  - Page 231, 1966-1967 (Box 18, Folder 22)
  - Page 232, 1966-1967 (Box 18, Folder 23)
  - Page 233, 1966-1967 (Box 18, Folder 24)
  - Page 234, 1966-1967 (Box 18, Folder 25)
  - Page 235, 1966-1967 (Box 18, Folder 26)
  - Page 236, 1966-1967 (Box 18, Folder 27)
  - Page 237, 1966-1967 (Box 18, Folder 28)
  - Page 238, 1966-1967 (Box 18, Folder 29)
  - Page 239, 1966-1967 (Box 18, Folder 30)
  - Page 240, 1966-1967 (Box 18, Folder 31)
  - Page 241, 1966-1967 (Box 18, Folder 32)
  - Page 242, 1966-1967 (Box 18, Folder 33)
  - Page 243, 1966-1967 (Box 18, Folder 34)
  - Page 244, 1966-1967 (Box 18, Folder 35)
  - Page 245, 1966-1967 (Box 18, Folder 36)
  - Page 246, 1966-1967 (Box 18, Folder 37)
  - Page 247, 1966-1967 (Box 18, Folder 38)
  - Page 248, 1966-1967 (Box 18, Folder 39)
  - Page 249, 1966-1967 (Box 18, Folder 40)
  - Page 250, 1966-1967 (Box 18, Folder 41)
  - Page 251, 1966-1967 (Box 18, Folder 42)
  - Page 252, 1966-1967 (Box 18, Folder 43)
  - Page 253, 1966-1967 (Box 18, Folder 44)
  - Page 254, 1966-1967 (Box 18, Folder 45)
  - Page 255, 1966-1967 (Box 18, Folder 46)
  - Page 256, 1966-1967 (Box 18, Folder 47)
  - Page 257, 1966-1967 (Box 18, Folder 48)
  - Page 258, 1966-1967 (Box 18, Folder 49)
  - Page 259, 1966-1967 (Box 18, Folder 50)
  - Page 260, 1966-1967 (Box 18, Folder 51)
  - Page 261, 1966-1967 (Box 18, Folder 52)
  - Page 262, 1966-1967 (Box 18, Folder 53)
  - Page 263, 1966-1967 (Box 18, Folder 54)
  - Page 264, 1966-1967 (Box 18, Folder 55)
  - Page 265, 1966-1967 (Box 18, Folder 56)
  - Page 266, 1966-1967 (Box 18, Folder 57)
  - Page 267, 1966-1967 (Box 18, Folder 58)
  - Page 268, 1966-1967 (Box 18, Folder 59)
  - Page 269, 1966-1967 (Box 18, Folder 60)
  - Page 270, 1966-1967 (Box 18, Folder 61)
  - Page 271, 1966-1967 (Box 18, Folder 62)
  - Page 272, 1966-1967 (Box 18, Folder 63)
  - Page 273, 1966-1967 (Box 18, Folder 64)
  - Page 274, 1966-1967 (Box 18, Folder 65)
  - Page 275, 1966-1967 (Box 18, Folder 66)
  - Page 276, 1966-1967 (Box 18, Folder 67)
  - Page 277, 1966-1967 (Box 18, Folder 68)
  - Page 278, 1966-1967 (Box 18, Folder 69)
  - Page 279, 1966-1967 (Box 18, Folder 70)
  - Page 280, 1966-1967 (Box 18, Folder 71)
  - Page 281, 1966-1967 (Box 18, Folder 72)
  - Page 282, 1966-1967 (Box 18, Folder 73)
  - Page 283, 1966-1967 (Box 18, Folder 74)
  - Page 284, 1966-1967 (Box 18, Folder 75)
  - Page 285, 1966-1967 (Box 18, Folder 76)
  - Page 286, 1966-1967 (Box 18, Folder 77)
  - Page 287, 1966-1967 (Box 18, Folder 78)
  - Page 288, 1966-1967 (Box 18, Folder 79)
  - Page 289, 1966-1967 (Box 18, Folder 80)
  - Page 290, 1966-1967 (Box 18, Folder 81)
  - Page 291, 1966-1967 (Box 18, Folder 82)
  - Page 292, 1966-1967 (Box 18, Folder 83)
  - Page 293, 1966-1967 (Box 18, Folder 84)
  - Page 294, 1966-1967 (Box 18, Folder 85)
  - Page 295, 1966-1967 (Box 18, Folder 86)
  - Page 296, 1966-1967 (Box 18, Folder 87)
  - Page 297, 1966-1967 (Box 18, Folder 88)
  - Page 298, 1966-1967 (Box 18, Folder 89)
  - Page 299, 1966-1967 (Box 18, Folder 90)
  - Page 300, 1966-1967 (Box 18, Folder 91)
  - Page 301, 1966-1967 (Box 18, Folder 92)
  - Page 302, 1966-1967 (Box 18, Folder 93)
  - Page 303, 1966-1967 (Box 18, Folder 94)
  - Page 304, 1966-1967 (Box 18, Folder 95)
  - Page 305, 1966-1967 (Box 18, Folder 96)
  - Page 306, 1966-1967 (Box 18, Folder 97)
  - Page 307, 1966-1967 (Box 18, Folder 98)
  - Page 308, 1966-1967 (Box 18, Folder 99)
  - Page 309, 1966-1967 (Box 18, Folder 100)
  - Page 310, 1966-1967 (Box 18, Folder 101)
  - Page 311, 1966-1967 (Box 18, Folder 102)
  - Page 312, 1966-1967 (Box 18, Folder 103)
  - Page 313, 1966-1967 (Box 18, Folder 104)
  - Page 314, 1966-1967 (Box 18, Folder 105)
  - Page 315, 1966-1967 (Box 18, Folder 106)
  - Page 316, 1966-1967 (Box 18, Folder 107)
  - Page 317, 1966-1967 (Box 18, Folder 108)
  - Page 318, 1966-1967 (Box 18, Folder 109)
  - Page 319, 1966-1967 (Box 18, Folder 110)
  - Page 320, 1966-1967 (Box 18, Folder 111)
  - Page 321, 1966-1967 (Box 18, Folder 112)
  - Page 322, 1966-1967 (Box 18, Folder 113)
  - Page 323, 1966-1967 (Box 18, Folder 114)
  - Page 324, 1966-1967 (Box 19, Folder 1)
  - Page 325, 1966-1967 (Box 19, Folder 2)
  - Page 326, 1966-1967 (Box 19, Folder 3)
  - Page 327, 1966-1967 (Box 19, Folder 4)
  - Page 328, 1966-1967 (Box 19, Folder 5)
  - Page 329, 1966-1967 (Box 19, Folder 6)
  - Page 330, 1966-1967 (Box 19, Folder 7)
  - Page 331, 1966-1967 (Box 19, Folder 8)
  - Page 332, 1966-1967 (Box 19, Folder 9)
  - Page 333, 1966-1967 (Box 19, Folder 10)
  - Page 334, 1966-1967 (Box 19, Folder 11)
  - Page 335, 1966-1967 (Box 19, Folder 12)
  - Page 336, 1966-1967 (Box 19, Folder 13)
  - Page 337, 1966-1967 (Box 19, Folder 14)
  - Page 338, 1966-1967 (Box 19, Folder 15)
  - Page 339, 1966-1967 (Box 19, Folder 16)
  - Page 340, 1966-1967 (Box 19, Folder 17)
  - Page 341, 1966-1967 (Box 19, Folder 18)
  - Page 342, 1966-1967 (Box 19, Folder 19)
  - Page 343, 1966-1967 (Box 19, Folder 20)
  - Page 344, 1966-1967 (Box 19, Folder 21)
  - Page 345, 1966-1967 (Box 19, Folder 22)
  - Page 346, 1966-1967 (Box 19, Folder 23)
  - Page 347, 1966-1967 (Box 19, Folder 24)
  - Page 348, 1966-1967 (Box 19, Folder 25)
  - Page 349, 1966-1967 (Box 19, Folder 26)
  - Page 350, 1966-1967 (Box 19, Folder 27)
  - Page 351, 1966-1967 (Box 19, Folder 28)
  - Page 352, 1966-1967 (Box 19, Folder 29)
  - Page 353, 1966-1967 (Box 19, Folder 30)
  - Page 354, 1966-1967 (Box 19, Folder 31)
  - Page 355, 1966-1967 (Box 19, Folder 32)
  - Page 356, 1966-1967 (Box 19, Folder 33)
  - Page 357, 1966-1967 (Box 19, Folder 34)
  - Page 358, 1966-1967 (Box 19, Folder 35)
  - Page 359, 1966-1967 (Box 19, Folder 36)
  - Page 360, 1966-1967 (Box 19, Folder 37)
  - Page 361, 1966-1967 (Box 19, Folder 38)
  - Page 362, 1966-1967 (Box 19, Folder 39)
  - Page 363, 1966-1967 (Box 19, Folder 40)
  - Page 364, 1966-1967 (Box 19, Folder 41)
  - Page 365, 1966-1967 (Box 19, Folder 42)
  - Page 366, 1966-1967 (Box 19, Folder 43)
  - Page 367, 1966-1967 (Box 19, Folder 44)
  - Page 368, 1966-1967 (Box 19, Folder 45)
  - Page 370, 1966-1967 (Box 19, Folder 47)
  - Page 371, 1966-1967 (Box 19, Folder 48)
  - Page 372, 1966-1967 (Box 19, Folder 49)
  - Page 373, 1966-1967 (Box 19, Folder 50)
  - Page 374, 1966-1967 (Box 19, Folder 51)
  - Page 375, 1966-1967 (Box 19, Folder 52)
  - Page 376, 1966-1967 (Box 19, Folder 53)
  - Page 377, 1966-1967 (Box 19, Folder 54)
  - Page 378, 1966-1967 (Box 19, Folder 55)
  - Page 379, 1966-1967 (Box 19, Folder 56)
  - Page 380, 1966-1967 (Box 19, Folder 57)
  - Page 381, 1966-1967 (Box 19, Folder 58)
  - Page 382, 1966-1967 (Box 19, Folder 59)
  - Page 383, 1966-1967 (Box 19, Folder 60)
  - Page 384, 1966-1967 (Box 19, Folder 61)
  - Page 385, 1966-1967 (Box 19, Folder 62)
  - Page 386, 1966-1967 (Box 19, Folder 63)
  - Page 387, 1966-1967 (Box 19, Folder 64)
  - Page 388, 1966-1967 (Box 19, Folder 65)
  - Page 389, 1966-1967 (Box 19, Folder 66)
  - Page 390, 1966-1967 (Box 19, Folder 67)
  - Page 391, 1966-1967 (Box 19, Folder 68)
  - Page 392, 1966-1967 (Box 19, Folder 69)
  - Page 393, 1966-1967 (Box 19, Folder 70)
  - Page 394, 1966-1967 (Box 19, Folder 71)
  - Page 395, 1966-1967 (Box 19, Folder 72)
  - Page 396, 1966-1967 (Box 19, Folder 73)
  - Page 397, 1966-1967 (Box 19, Folder 74)
  - Page 398, 1966-1967 (Box 19, Folder 75)
  - Page 399, 1966-1967 (Box 19, Folder 76)
  - Page 400, 1966-1967 (Box 19, Folder 77)
  - Page 401, 1966-1967 (Box 19, Folder 78)
  - Page 402, 1966-1967 (Box 19, Folder 79)
  - Page 403, 1966-1967 (Box 19, Folder 80)
  - Page 404, 1966-1967 (Box 19, Folder 81)
  - Page 405, 1966-1967 (Box 19, Folder 82)
  - Page 406, 1966-1967 (Box 19, Folder 83)
  - Page 407, 1966-1967 (Box 19, Folder 84)
  - Page 408, 1966-1967 (Box 19, Folder 85)
  - Page 409, 1966-1967 (Box 19, Folder 86)
  - Page 410, 1966-1967 (Box 19, Folder 87)
  - Page 411, 1966-1967 (Box 19, Folder 88)
  - Page 412, 1966-1967 (Box 19, Folder 89)
  - Page 413, 1966-1967 (Box 19, Folder 90)
  - Page 414, 1966-1967 (Box 19, Folder 91)
  - Page 415, 1966-1967 (Box 19, Folder 92)
  - Page 416, 1966-1967 (Box 19, Folder 93)
  - Page 417, 1966-1967 (Box 19, Folder 94)
  - Page 418, 1966-1967 (Box 19, Folder 95)
  - Page 419, 1966-1967 (Box 19, Folder 96)
  - Page 420, 1966-1967 (Box 19, Folder 97)
  - Page 421, 1966-1967 (Box 19, Folder 98)
  - Page 422, 1966-1967 (Box 19, Folder 99)
  - Page 423, 1966-1967 (Box 19, Folder 100)
  - Page 424, 1966-1967 (Box 19, Folder 101)
  - Page 425, 1966-1967 (Box 19, Folder 102)
  - Page 426, 1966-1967 (Box 19, Folder 103)
  - Page 427, 1966-1967 (Box 19, Folder 104)
  - Miscellaneous Items, 1966-1967 (Box 19, Folder 105)